synergyworldwide.com 2007-10-24

# Privacy Statement

|  |  |    
|  |    
|    
  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
| 

Keeping customer information secure is a top priority for Synergy WorldWide Products. Please read Synergy WorldWide’s privacy policy below. This policy outlines our views and practices and how they pertain to you as a visitor to synergyworldwide.com. Please check back periodically, as these policies may change. However, our fundamental commitment to protecting visitors’ privacy will not change. 

  1. What information does Synergy WorldWide collect on the Web site?
  2. How is the information used?
  3. Does Synergy WorldWide share my information?
  4. How secure is my information?
  5. What if I have more questions?

****

| **1.  What Information Does Synergy WorldWide Collect on the Website?**  
---  
  
  * **Information You Volunteer.** We only collect personal information that you volunteer while using our services. You may always choose not to provide information. (Visitors may access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing personal data.) 
  * **Information Collected Automatically.** We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. Like most Web sites, we use cookies, or data files automatically stored on your computer, to enhance your visit to our site. In general, cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information unless you as a visitor supply the information knowingly. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We use cookies to store such information as temporary session IDs and your Distributor ID number (if you mark the checkbox on the login page). We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. Synergy WorldWide does not collect information about you from other sources, e.g., public records or bodies, or private organizations. 

**2.  How Does Synergy WorldWide Use the Information It Collects?**  
---  
  
  * We use the information we collect on the site to enhance your overall experience while visiting the site and to preserve the integrity of our compensation plan. 
  * We do not collect or use personal data for any purposes outside of customer service, site administration, online shopping and company communication. If we wish to use personal data for any other purpose, we always obtain your consent first. 

**3.  Does Synergy WorldWide share my information with others?**  
---  
  
  * No. Synergy WorldWide does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to any outside parties. We value our customers’ privacy and will not jeopardize our relationship with customers by selling their information to solicitors. 

**4.  How secure is my information?**  
---  
  
  * Synergy WorldWide uses Secure Socket Layers (SSL) to ensure a secure connection whenever transmitting or receiving personal information. With SSL, information transmitted between two computers via the Internet is sent in an encrypted format so that only the sending and receiving computers can decode it. SSL ensures that no one intercepts any of your personal information while it is being transferred to us. A secure connection is maintained until the checkout process is either completed or canceled. 
  * Synergyworldwide.com is a VeriSign Secure Site. This means that VeriSign, a trusted leader in Internet security, has issued and verified the legitimacy of Synergy WorldWide’s SSL certificate. For more information, click on the VeriSign Secure Site logo found throughout our Web site. 
  * Synergy WorldWide maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your personal information. We strive to comply with all applicable national laws and global/regional regulatory schemes. We also self-regulate the collection and use of personal data. 
  * Employees who have access to personal data are obligated to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data and are held to the highest standards of integrity in utilizing, storing or retrieving this data. 

5. What if I have more questions?  
---  
Direct inquiries or concerns about our privacy policy t  

> Customer Service   
> Synergy WorldWide  
> 5152 N. Edgewood Drive  
> Suite #200  
> Provo, Utah 84604  
> (801) 431-7660  
> hotline@synergyworldwide.com

Please summarize the nature of your question in the subject line of any email you send. 

Thank you for reviewing this policy.

|     

|
